I salute Rajesh, I welcome you
today, I am starting with a real story,
it was a Saturday, I had
returned home after working in the post office, I was very
happy because I was young, if you too had said
that I have to go to the doctor, it had happened, it had been
barely 5 minutes when
both of us screamed,
we both were under the truck, it was about to
run over us, but thank God, the stop of
our motorcycle got stuck in that cycle
and the truck stopped there, but both of us were injured,
someone has rightly said that accidents do
not happen with warning, at that time I
understood that war and appointment, friends,
appointment and if you arrive on time, then there is an
appointment under it, friends, we have gone to the
hospital and we have subscribed and
our bank balance has been debited quickly,
but this charge is so much that
confusion arises, through this video we will
discuss whether we should
take a mediclaim policy, what
precautions should we take while taking a plane, so that we can
hug easily, some people say that I am
healthy now, I do not need it, friends,
insurance can be taken only when  If
we are not healthy, then the
subscription gets exhausted sooner than the appointment
and we need a plane.
Secondly, today's lifestyle has become very
physical activity-less, there is a lot of stress, due to which
they are not necessary for subscription. One more
thing is that the appointment subscription is too much,
so I suggest that the policy should be
taken as early as possible.
Another saying is that the appointment size
makes our health worthy, similarly,
that turmeric can be
subscribed as early as possible. First, due to an
accident, second, due to a reason, third, by
regular subscription.
Today we will specifically discuss this. I would like to mention
one more thing,
friends, when we are admitted to a hospital, the
mediclaim policy
covers our medical expenses, but
because our other expenses are ongoing,
which can be covered through our quality
and this is very cheap. ₹500 deductible.
This can be taken separately or along with the policy.
First in a good to-do list should be free health checkup, there should be a
good hospital network,
post hydration.  There should be a
deduction of room rent in live with a clear,
more time restore benefit ambulance
facility and attention should be paid to this and
not everyone needs more APN,
you can take
subscription as per the need, you can get a small subscription for
this disgusting mission hospital, after getting admitted in the hospital the
company's team has to give us information about it,
in a mediclaim we can clean it in two ways,
one cashless second embarrassment,
for cashless we have to get admitted in a network hospital
where we get
admitted by showing our work policy bond approved,
it is of two types, one
plant second in emergency a few days before the
insurance company gives all its information and
subscribes,
in emergency this updater located in the hospital does the same work
and sends all the bail
reports etc. to the insurance company,
due to which Islam gets it in India,
secondly if we take the patient to a network hospital then
we do it first and then
get it back from the company, the need for subscription is
like disgusting towards it, due to which
definitely subscribe and appointment here
some people have subscribed and if it has to be
submitted then they submit it to the association,
I have given two here  I would like to mention one more precaution:
after installing the device for all the bills,
get a photocopy of the appointment number so that
we can tell you that you will get the paper on that number.
Now comes the matter of claim form. Claim
forms are of 2004. Part A and Part B
text is always written by the policyholder.
Sometimes signatures are missed here.
Please note that this is very important
which has to be collected from the hospital.
Here it is important to ensure that the
date and time is written on the discharge card so that
you can submit the
last process. Paper submission is done
date wise. The concerned company keeps
giving the papers to the passengers and after a few
days your payment comes. Here is
another important discussion that we can
support. If someone needs another tip of Rs. 10 lakh and
instead of buying a plan of Rs. 10 lakh, if we
buy a mediclaim plan of Rs. 5 lakh and a super top up loan of Rs. 5 lakh, then the cover becomes Rs. 10
lakh. But by doing this, it becomes the main thing
that this combination can be anything.  It is 3 lakh
or 7 lakh, you can do it as per your wish,
number two family members, Jhalasa
is available on Thursday, as many as can be subscribed, should be
taken together,
phone number 3 floater policy, understand one thing in this, the
whole family is there, hence it is
cheaper, you can see this, I
hope that I will give you some
related information, if you need any other information then
my mobile number is 90,
thank you for watching my video, may you always
be healthy, our best wishes